Checking in - how are you doing?
Many of your first conversations in English are people asking you how your're doing
and about your preferences and choices.
So this video is to help you with that language.
You’ll get asked about what you want and if you’re OK quite often while you’re settling in.
Do you want coffee? Do you want tea?
Yes; no; maybe; I’m not sure
Are you OK? Fine, thanks. Are you OK? No, I’m not well.
Are you ready now? Sure.
Let’s practise ‘do you want?’ and ‘are you OK?’ as we use those a lot.
D'you want a pen?
So it's not 'do you', it's d'you
Is it 'do you' or 'd'you'? 'D'you'.
Yes, so we take 'do you', and put them together, 'd'you'
D'you want a pen? Yes thanks. Here you are...
Are you OK?
And it's the same, OK. That's great, that's very good, yes.
Fine thanks
Are you OK? Maybe, I'm not sure.