Directions
Sometimes people feel a bit anxious about going outside in a new place in case they get lost.
This language is to help you ask for directions and understand when people tell you where to go.
The first two are things for you to say,
and this is for you to understand and listen when other people speak.
Straight ahead
Turn left
Turn right
Over there
A bit further down
Just around the corner
So, let's practise:
Excuse me, where's the supermarket
supermarket
the supermarket
where's the supermarket?
Excuse me, where's the supermarket
I'm a bit lost
lost
bit lost
a bit lost
I'm a bit lost.
Now let's practice listening
You're nearly there.
It’s just over the road.
Keep going until the lights.
Straight ahead
Turn left
Turn right
Over there
A bit further down
Just around the corner
Thank you!
You’re welcome.