Filling in forms and making appointments
In this video we’re learning language to help you answer the questions
you’ll be asked when you’re filling in a form.
What’s your first name? What’s your surname? What’s your date of birth?
What’s your postcode? What’s your national insurance number?
What’s your NHS number? Who’s your doctor?
What's your first name?
What's your surname?
What's your date of birth?
What's your postcode?
What's your national insurance number?
What's your NHS number?
Who's your doctor?
If someone’s helping you fill in a form they might tell you
the time you need to go there, making an appointment, just like at the doctors.
This video helps you talk about appointment times.
What time’s my appointment? It’s at 3.40
Sorry, I’m a bit late. Don’t worry, it’s good to see you.
Sorry, I’m a bit early. Don’t worry, it’s good to see you
Let’s practise how to ask about appointment times.
What time’s my appointment?