Introduction
Hello and welcome. I’m Jos, a teacher from the UK with years of experience helping people learn spoken English.
We know that some of you are not able to speak English or communicate effectively with those around you. Don't worry, we have designed this free fully translated course for you, focusing on really useful everyday language.
Jos’s videos show you how to talk with others informally, using language other people will find friendly and easy to understand.
The videos also help with pronunciation so you can speak at the same speed as people in the UK.
For complete beginners we start from the basics, which are writing and sounding out the English alphabet, numbers, and easy things to say.
For non-beginners, skip the phonics picture section and use the videos and workbook to learn more conversational speech and expressions, and develop your fluency skills.
Each lesson is accompanied by a video so you can watch a teacher, and hear and practice speaking the language in the book. This focus on speaking and listening will make it easier both for you to understand English speakers, and to speak in a way they will understand.
If you have a printed copy of the workbook, then scanning the QR code on each page will direct you to the video.
Good luck, study well, and enjoy!