Language for looking after children
If you have children they can be a natural connection point for talking to other people.
In the UK we have lots of parent and toddler groups for pre-school children.
You might meet in the playground, or you might talk to other parents when you’re waiting
to drop your kids off at school, or pick them up.
So we’re going to look at some of the language to help you with those conversations.
So let’s practise some of the language you might need
when you’re with your children and other families.
“Where are the toilets please? They’re over there’
“Does he need a drink? Yes please.’
‘We’re going to the park, do you want to come?
Did he hurt himself? No, he’s OK thanks.
“Where are the toilets please? They’re over there’
Are the kids OK? They’re just a bit bored. Shall we tidy the toys now?
Do they need a drink? Thanks, that’s great.
Does he need something to eat? Thanks, what have you got?
We’re going to the park on Sunday at 1 o’clock. Do you want to come?
Where are the toilets please?
They’re over there. So listen. That’s it, yes.
Does he need a drink, or does she need a drink for a girl.
Yes, that’s good. So this one – ‘We’re going to the park’.
Do you want to come? So it’s ‘d’you want’.
We don’t say ‘do you want’. D’you want to come? Very good.