Leaving the room
If you have English speaking guests or you're doing something with English-speaking people you might need to leave and come back, and this language will help you explain
Hey, how are you getting on?
Are you ready?
I'm just going to help my mother-in-law.
I'm just going to pray.
I won't be long.
I'll be back in 10 minutes.
Shall we practice? - Yes
I need to go now.
Are you ready?
I won't be long.
I'll be back in 10 minutes.
To pray.
Going to pray.
I'm just going to pray.
I'm just going to help my mother.
Are you ready?
I won't be long.
Be long
won't be long
I won't be long.
I'll be back in 10 minutes.
10 minutes
in 10 minutes
back in 10 minutes
I'll be back in 10 minutes.
to pray
going to pray
I'm just going to pray.
I'm just going to help my mother.
help my mother
going to help my mother
I'm just going to help my mother.