Making plans to meet up
This video teaches you language to ask people to meet and do something together.
It’s really important for your wellbeing and mental health to spend time with your friends,
and it’s also important for children to meet up with their friends outside school
and have time to play together.
Shall we meet at the weekend? Sure, how about on Sunday?
Fine. What time? How about 11? OK.
So, let’s practise the questions and answers.
Shall we meet at the weekend?
How about on Sunday?
Where are you?
Should we meet at the weekend?
One more. It’s quite difficult isn’t it? We’ll try it one more time.
Shall we meet at the weekend?
And can you hear it, ‘shu' we meet? You don't say the 'll'. You just say, 'shu' we meet for the weekend? Excellent!
So it's just, Sh'll we meet for the weekend?
Ok, shall we do this one? How about on Sunday?
In English we almost sing, you know we go up and down.
So,‘How about on Sunday?
Can you try? ‘How about on Sunday?’ Good, I like the eyebrows!
Where are you? Difficult. So, ‘where are you?’