Making new friends
These are the things you might want to say or you might hear other people say when you're starting to meet someone for the first time and you want to make friends with them.
So, a lot of these things are positive appreciation and that's obviously a very good way to make friends with people, to say nice things to them.
Do you mind if I join you?
What's your number?
Can I bring my children?
It's been lovely to see you.
See you next time.
I'll see you next week.
Thanks for your help, I really appreciate it.
How old are your children?
Thank you, you've been very kind.
This is really great.
So, let's practice.
Do you mind if I join you?
join you
if I join you
mind if I join you
Do you mind if I join you?
What’s your number?
number
your number
What’s your number?
Can I bring my children?
It's been lovely to see you.
see you
to see you
lovely to see you
It's been lovely to see you.
See you next time.
next time
you next time
See you next time!
I'll see you next week.
next week
see you next week
I'll see you next week.
Thanks for your help, I really appreciate it.
appreciate it
I really appreciate it
thanks for your help
How old are your children?
your children
are your children
How old are your children?
You've been really kind, thanks.
kind thanks
really kind thanks
You've been really kind, thanks.
And the last one…
This is really great!
really great