Medical support
This video is to help you understand some of the things you might hear at the hospital or at the doctors.
First, we're going to practise a couple of things to say and then we're going to listen to some of the things you might hear.
Hi
Can you just wait to be called please?
Can you come through, please?
Just follow the blue line.
Do you have any allergies?
No.
Do you get free prescriptions?
Yes.
Can I have an interpreter please?
Yes. Would you like a chaperone?
No thank-you.
Is it done now?
Let's practice…
interpreter please
have an interpreter please
Can I have an interpreter please?
Very good.
And this question for when you think it's OK, they're done and you can go, but you want to check.
So, let's practice
done now
Is it done now?
These are the things you might hear that you want to understand.
Wait to be called.
Can you come through please?
Do you have any allergies?
Do you get free prescriptions?
Do you want a chaperone?
And this last one is for hospitals which are very big, so they have colour systems to help you find your way.
So, somebody might tell you, 'Follow the blue line',
and then you look for the blue line , and you follow it to get to the right part of the hospital.