Saying hello
We’re going to learn how to say, ‘Hi, how are you? Fine thanks, you?’
There are different ways to greet people in English.
Here are some that you might hear when you’re outside.
Hi, how are you? Fine, thanks, you? Yes, fine.
How you doing? Yes, good, you? I’m OK.
Alright? Yeah, you?
In English we speak fast, and when we do
we join the words together and change the sounds we make.
We’re going to teach you to speak this way,
so that when you’re outside, you can understand what people are saying to you.
So here’s the example, with ‘hi, how are you?’
Hi, how are you? Fine, thanks, you?
We make some words stronger, and we call it 'word stress'
When you see the red, that's where the words are strong.
Hi, how are you? Fine thanks, you?