Talking about possessions
Talking about what belongs to who happens more often than you might think.
Is this yours?
Whose is it?
It’s mine
It’s yours
It’s his
It’s hers
It’s ours
It’s theirs
My mum’s name
My dad’s car
And you can see the ‘s’ –put an ‘s’ when something belongs to somebody. Jos’s glasses.
Is this yours? No it’s not mine, it’s yours. Is this yours? No, it’s not mine, it’s theirs.
Whose is this? I think it’s his. Whose is this? It’s not ours.
This is my dad’s name. That’s my mum’s car.
Is this yours?
Crazy English, pronunciation.
So when we ask a question, we often go up and down.
Whose is it?
It's mine
It's yours
It's his
It's hers
It's ours
It's theirs
Good, thats really good. How about this one?
My mum’s name
My dad's car