Talking about the weather
If you meet somebody for the first time you might talk about personal things straight away,
but here in the UK you don’t do that – you talk about non-personal things.
So this might be when you’re passing your neighbour in the street,
or if you’re at the queue in the bus stop or in the supermarket.
A really popular topic is the weather.
Once you’ve spoken to someone casually maybe 2 or 3 times,
or if you’re meeting someone more ‘officially’
(like your child’s new teacher or a new neighbour or somebody that your friend is introducing you to)
then you can talk about more personal things,
maybe how your children are getting on at school, or whether you like the area that you’re in.
So we’re going to learn language to talk about the weather,
because you can use that with everyone, all the time. Let’s listen to people talking about the weather:
Nice today, isn’t it? Yes, lovely. Bit cold today isn’t it? Yeah, freezing.
Now let’s practice how to say this and make the right sounds:
Nice today, isn't it? - Yes.
Bit cold today, isn't it? - Yes.
So let’s try this bit: ‘isn’t it?’ Nice today. Very good!