Talking About  What You Want And Need
In English there are several ways to ask about what you want or need,
so we’re going to let you listen to some now
so that you can understand what people are saying when they speak to you.
Then at the end I’ll help you practice a few simple ones you can use when you want to ask for something.
Have you got a pen please? Sure, here you are. Thanks.
Have you got the time please? Yes, it’s 2.40.
Do you need a break now? Yes, I’m tired.
Can you pass me that pen please? Yeah, there you go.
Shall we swap these over? Yeah, good idea.
Which one? This one or that one? This one please. Here you go.
Which one, this one or that one? Both, please. Here you go
I don’t know what I’m doing, can you help me? OK.
Let’s practise asking for what you want and need in a really simple, easy way.
Can I have a pen please? Can you help me please?
and this is the same here, can you help me please?
That's good.