What time is it?
There are two ways to tell the time,
The digital clock and the traditional clock.
The digital clock is much easier, so for example: 10:25
The bad news is that in the UK lots of people use this traditional clock to tell the time.
This circle is one hour, and there are 60 minutes in an hour.
On zero minutes, we say '2 o'clock'
So, we look at 'half', 2 halves, we talk about half an hour - that's 30 minutes.
So… half past 2.
Or if we move this one, maybe half past 4.
Fifteen minutes is a quarter of an hour.
This is a quarter.
So we say, 'quarter past 4'.
It means 'quarter of an hour past 4', but that's very long, so we say 'quarter past' for short.
So this whole section is talking about what's after the hour, or 'past' 4.
So if for example it's 5 minutes… 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 - it's '5 past 4'.
Or maybe it's 10 minutes after, so… 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10… '10 past 4'.
Here is 5, 10, 15, 20 minutes, so 20 past 4.
And here another 5 minutes, 25 minutes so 25 past 4.
So, when we come round to this side of the clock, we're thinking about the next hour we're coming to.
So for example, quarter of an hour until 5.
Quarter 'to' 5.
Here, it's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 minutes until 5 o'clock
So we say, '5 to 5'.
Or '5 to 2'.
Or maybe - '5 to 4'.
Now we have 5, 10, 15, 20 minutes until 4, so we say, '20 to 4'.
So we're going to practice now
4 o'clock
5 past 4.
10 past 4.
Quarter past 4.
20 past 4.
25 past 4.
And half past 4.
25 to 5.
20 to 5.
Quarter to 5.