Who were you with?
Talking about what you did, people might ask you who you were with.
As a beginner you don’t need to be able to ask these questions,
but it can be useful to be able to understand and use simple language
about family and friends to explain.
Who did you go with? With my friend and her children.
Who did you go with? With my brother and sister.
Son, Daughter. Brother, sister. Mum, Dad.
Grandad, Grandma. Aunt, Uncle, Cousin.
So let’s practice the question and answer.
Who did you go with?
With my friend and her children.
With my daughter.
Who did you go with? Great - Really good!
With my friend and her children. Yes.
So we’re making the sounds very short, yes.
OK, how about this one?
With my daughter.
Great.
Let’s learn the words for family members:
Daughter
Son
Sister
Brother
Husband
Wife
Mother or mum
Father or dad
Grandad
Grandma
Uncle
Aunt
Cousin
Sister in law
Brother in law
Mother in law
Father in law