Writing letter shapes
Now we’re going to show you how to make the shapes of the letters.
You start with the black line,
and you keep your pencil or pen on the paper board until you've finished that letter.
So getting the curved circle shapes of the letters right can take a bit of practice,
sometimes people squash them or get them in the wrong direction.
So we really want to go all the way round and make a good big circle for a lot of these letters.
It goes across, and then round like this
So you can see that my letters are sitting on the line – we haven’t got them up floating,
we’ve got them down, touching.
And when I write a word, the letters are close together.
We don’t want big gaps, like this.we want them close.
So these letters go up higher in the air than the other ones.
so you need to make them nice and tall, OK?
And these ones the letters go down under the line
so you don’t want your ‘g’ to sit like this, it has to have a tail which hangs down.
The other letters just sit on the line.
So we want to leave a small space between each word.
And then when you get even better, you can make your letters smaller,
and put your words closer together.
It takes practice but you will see your writing getting neater and neater over time.