Your hopes for the future
Being able to talk about what you want in the future makes it more likely that people can help you and more likely that you'll make it happen.
These are things that people have told us they would like for their futures and maybe some of them are true for you too.
I'd like to get a job.
I'd like to get married and have a family. I want to study computer science.
I want to get my house sorted out. I want to learn to drive.
I want to go to college. I want to save some money.
I'd like to get out more. I want to learn more about history.
I'd like to make some new friends.
I'd like to get a job.
I'd like to get married and have a family.
I want to go to college.
I want to study.
I want to get my house sorted out.
I want to learn to drive.
I want to save some money.
I'd like to get out more.
I want to learn more about…
And the last one,
I'd like to make some new friends.
And good luck with your future!
Thank-you.